Contact

sw2.bae@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sangbae-8a38011a0 (LinkedIn) sw2bae.github.io/portfolio_Sang-Woo-Bae/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Software Testing
Web Development
Project Management

Certifications

KU Full-Stack Flex Coding Boot Camp

Sang Bae

Full Stack Web Developer / SW QA Engineer

Kansas City Metropolitan Area

Summary

[Experience]

 Samsung Electronics of America (SEA)

-SW Quality Assurance

Engineer

-Special Project Planner/Analyst

[Portfolio Website]

https://sw2bae.github.io/portfolio_Bae/

[GitHub]

https://github.com/sw2bae

[Education]

University of Washington, Seattle, WA

Major: B.A. Mathematics

University of Kansas, Lawrence, KS

Course: Coding Boot Camp

[Skills]

- •Full Stack Web Developing (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Web API, Node JS, MySQL, Mongo, React)
- •XCAP/XCAL Data analyzing (HPUE)
- •Fundamental QXDM Log analyzing through QCAT (QAM/MIMO/ ORNL/CA)
- •Fundamental IMS Log / SIP IMS Call Flow analyzing (VoWIFI/ VoLTE)
- Data Analyzing through SAP and SMES
- Bilingual English, Korean

Experience

Samsung Electronics America 5 years 6 months

SW Quality Assurance Engineer
July 2016 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Overland Park, Kansas, United States

- Creating/Maintaining an internal programs/ tools (React.JS)
- •Global Best Employee Award 5G Project (April 2020)
- •5G TF Team member Creating/Performing 5G HW/SW Performance Test cases (June 2018 Current)
- •Planning Samsung Flagship Models HW/SW Performance Tests (Galaxy S8/S9/S10,S20 Galaxy Note 8/9/10)
- •Driving Sprint First VoLTE MR Test (Sep/Oct 2018)
- •Performing Sprint TM9 Beam Foaming feature test (May/June 2018)
- •Driving the first Samsung Chipset Model Protocol IOT Test Trip (March 2018)
- •Participating/Presenting at Automation Tools workshop in HQ, Korea (August 2017)
- •Performing Sprint HPUE feature Test / Post processing TOB result through XCAP tool
- Creating/performing test cases for Sprint Massive MIMO/QAM/ULCA features
- •Participating SMF joint meeting with Sprint (Q4'16/Q1'17)
- Participating weekly PM Meeting (June 2018 Current)

Special Project Planner/Analyst May 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 3 months) Coppell, Texas, United States

- •Planning weekly rework production requirements in timely manner based on customers' delivery schedules for each carrier (TMO/VZW/ATT/SPR/ACG/USC)
- •Managing production plan for Galaxy S7 Phase and User Trial samples for each customers.
- Analyzing BOM list of project models and placing an order through procurement team
- •Driving and managing shipping schedules through logistic team for project deliveries
- •Developing production line capacities with engineering team
- •Calculating task time and unit price to populate planning data base
- Data Analyzing through SAP and SMES

Education

The University of Kansas

KU Lifelong & Professional & Education, Completing Bootcamp · (2020 - 2020)

University of Washington

Bachelor's degree, Mathematics · (2010 - 2014)